Library. University Librarian. Administrative files UARC.0377
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Film Archives: Automated Access to Media and Media-Related Materials at UCLA, 1984; 891340 (Box 325, Folder 10)
- Getty, 1984-1985; 891341 (Box 325, Folder 11)
- Library Council's Report of the Investigation of the Library Assistant Series (with appendices), 1979; 891354 (Box 325, Folder 12)
- Library Council - Investigation of the Library Assistant Series (includes reports and responses), 1977-1979; 891353 (Box 325, Folder 13)
- Markey, 1986-1988; 891351 (Box 325, Folder 14)
- Map Library, 1981-1986; 891342 (Box 325, Folder 15)
- Melvyl, 1985; 891339 (Box 325, Folder 16)
- Melvyl statistics, 1990-1991; 891338 (Box 325, Folder 17)
- OAC (Office of Academic Computing) correspondence, 1985-1986; 891337 (Box 325, Folder 18)
- OCLC correspondence, 1985; 891336 (Box 325, Folder 19)
- OCLC invoices and transfers of expense, 1985-1986; 891335 (Box 325, Folder 20)
- Proposed Library Specialist Series (including comments from staff), 1980-1981; 891355 (Box 325, Folder 21)
- Technical Services (UCLA Library) Information Bulletin nos. 1-3, 1980-1982; 891352 (Box 325, Folder 22)
- Telecommunications., 1979-1982.; 891334 (Box 326, Folder 1)
- RLIN (Research Libraries Information Network)., 1979-1981.; 891333 (Box 326, Folder 2)
- OCLC., 1980-1984.; 891332 (Box 326, Folder 3-4)
- OCLC software., 1985-1988.; 891331 (Box 326, Folder 5)
- OCLC M300 workstation., 891330 (Box 326, Folder 6)
- OAC (Office of Academic Computing) Operations., 1982.; 891329 (Box 326, Folder 7)
- Biomedical Library., 1981-1985.; 891328 (Box 326, Folder 8)
- Advisory Committee on Cataloging Policy (ACCP)., 1983.; 891327 (Box 326, Folder 9-10)
- Conser correspondence, etc., 1983-1985.; 891326 (Box 326, Folder 11)
- Division of Library Automation (DLA)., 1981-1984.; 891325; Includes bulletin (Box 326, Folder 12-18)
- UCLA Library Resource Requirements., 891320 (Box 326, Folder 19)
- Working Group on Public Catalogs Subgroup B., 891319 (Box 326, Folder 20)
- Management Review and Analysis Program. Appendices of the Organization Task Force., 1976.; 891318 (Box 326, Folder 21)
- Library holdings statistics., 1967-1972.; 891317 (Box 326, Folder 22)
- Gifts and Exchanges Division, reorganization., 1976.; 891316 (Box 326, Folder 23)
- Wade, Ronald Ellis theft case., 891315 (Box 326, Folder 24)
- University of California Libraries - a plan for development, drafts., 1976-1977.; 891314 (Box 326, Folder 25)
- OCLC totcat network billings pre-1981., 1979-1981.; 891313 (Box 327, Folder 1)
- Public Access Advisory Committee (PAAC)., 891312 (Box 327, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs Service pre-1981., 1969-1980.; 891311 (Box 327, Folder 3)
- RLIN., 1980-1981.; 891310 (Box 327, Folder 4)
- OCLC correspondence., 891309 (Box 327, Folder 5)
- OCLC totcat network billings., 1982.; 891308 (Box 327, Folder 6)
- OCLC correspondence., 1977.; 891307 (Box 327, Folder 7)
- Division of Library Automation (DLA)., 891306 (Box 327, Folder 8)
- Map Library., 1979-1981.; 891305 (Box 327, Folder 9)
- Office of Academic Computing (OAC); Akren, Russ, intern Fall 1981 OAC terminal statistics and report., 891304 (Box 327, Folder 10)
- OCLC correspondence., 1982.; 891303 (Box 327, Folder 11)
- Advisory Committee on Cataloging Policy (ACCP)., 1979; 1981-1982.; 891302 (Box 327, Folder 12-15)
- Conser correspondence, etc., 1977-1982.; 891301 (Box 327, Folder 16)
- Technical Services Directors of Large Research Libraries (Discussion Group)., 1974; 1979-1983.; 891300 (Box 327, Folder 17)
- Technical Services Department (TSD) statistics., 1981-1982.; 891299 (Box 327, Folder 18-19)
- Map Library., 891298 (Box 327, Folder 20)
- Melvyl., 1980-1984.; 891297 (Box 327, Folder 21-22)
- Division of Library Automation., 891296 (Box 327, Folder 23)
- OCLC Totcat network billings., 1983.; 891295 (Box 328, Folder 1-2)
- ORION User Services., 891294 (Box 328, Folder 3)
- University of California, Irvine., 1981-1984.; 891293 (Box 328, Folder 4)
- University of California, Berkeley., 1982-1984.; 891292 (Box 328, Folder 5)
- Technical Services Directors of Large Research Libraries (Discussion Group)., 1984-1985.; 891291 (Box 328, Folder 6)
- Technical Services Department (TSD) statistics., 1983-1984.; 891290 (Box 328, Folder 7-8)
- Task Force., 891289 (Box 328, Folder 9)
- Technical Services Department (TSD)., 1979-1985.; 891288 (Box 328, Folder 10)
- Task Force Project Request Form., 1984-1985.; 891287 (Box 328, Folder 11)
- OCLC Invoices and Transfers of Expense., 891286 (Box 328, Folder 12)
- OCLC Invoices - Transfers of Expense., 1984-1985.; 891285 (Box 328, Folder 13)
- OCLC correspondence., 1984.; 891284 (Box 328, Folder 14-15)
- OCLC Totcat network billings., 1984.; 891283 (Box 328, Folder 16)
- Research Libraries Information Network (RLIN)., 1979.; 891282 (Box 328, Folder 17)
- SCUBAS (Steering Committee on the University's Bibliographic Access System)., 1977-1979.; 891281 (Box 328, Folder 18)
- Technical Services Department (TSD) reorganization., 1980.; 891280 (Box 328, Folder 19)
- OCLC Totcat network billings., 1981.; 891279 (Box 328, Folder 20)
- Request for Resource statements, revised 1977 May 17., 891278 (Box 328, Folder 21)
- Lending Code Revision Committee, Final Report of the 4/18/77., 1977.; 891277 (Box 328, Folder 22)
- Division of Library Automation (DLA)., 1985.; 891276 (Box 328, Folder 23)
- Scherrei, Rita chronological file (Administrative Systems and Personnel Services)., 1984-1988.; 891275 (Box 329, Folder 1-5)
- Miscellaneous questionnaires, surveys and other information., 1987-1991.; 891274 (Box 329, Folder 6-8)
- Report of Holdings, 1985; 891273 (Box 329, Folder 9)
- UC report of holdings., 891272 (Box 329, Folder 10)
- ARL statistics controversy., 1985.; 891271 (Box 329, Folder 11)
- ARL statistics., 1984-1985.; 891270 (Box 329, Folder 12)
- Holdings report., 891269 (Box 329, Folder 13)
- Unified Annual Report of Holdings., 1973-1981.; 891268 (Box 329, Folder 14-21)
- Unified Annual Report., 891267 (Box 329, Folder 22)
- Report of Public Service., 1981/1982.; 891266 (Box 329, Folder 23)
- Unit Dollar Values for Library Materials/Capitalization., 1983/1984.; 891265 (Box 329, Folder 24)
- Unit Dollar Value., 1982/1983.; 891264 (Box 329, Folder 25)
- Budget and FTE tables., 1982-1984.; 891263 (Box 329, Folder 26-27)
- ARL statistics worksheet., 891262 (Box 329, Folder 28)
- Circulations User Cats., 1983/1984.; 891261 (Box 329, Folder 29)
- Report of Public Services., 891260 (Box 329, Folder 30)
- Report of Public Services., 891259 (Box 329, Folder 31)
- Clark Library Acquisition Report., 1983/1984.; 891258 (Box 329, Folder 32)
- Annual Library Acquisition Report., 1982-1985.; 891257 (Box 329, Folder 33-35)
- Salary Surveys., 1975-1984.; 891256 (Box 329, Folder 36)
- Unified Annual reports schedule E., 891255 (Box 329, Folder 37)
- OCLC Electronic Document Delivery Survey., 1985.; 891254 (Box 329, Folder 38)
- ARL statistics questionnaire: University Expenditures U.S. Libraries., 1981/1982.; 891253 (Box 329, Folder 39)
- ARL statistics questionnaire., 1981-1984.; 891252 (Box 329, Folder 40-41)
- Unaffiliated libraries., 1983/1984.; 891251 (Box 329, Folder 42)
- California Academic Library Report., 891250 (Box 329, Folder 43)
- Report of Holdings, 1982-1984; 891249 (Box 329, Folder 44-46)
- User Services Summary., 1990-1991.; 891248 (Box 330, Folder 1)
- Public Services statistics., 1983/1984.; 891247 (Box 330, Folder 2)
- Orion circulation data., 891246 (Box 330, Folder 3)
- Unaffiliated libraries., 891245 (Box 330, Folder 4-5)
- Maryland Advisory Council. Professional Library Staff Salary Survey., 1986.; 891244 (Box 330, Folder 6)
- American Library Association Staff Composition Study., 1985.; 891243 (Box 330, Folder 7)
- University of Washington Libraries survey and compiled data on gender and ethnic origin of librarians., 1989.; 891242 (Box 330, Folder 8)
- Brigham Young University brittle books questionnaire., 1985.; 891241 (Box 330, Folder 9)
- Library Assistants and MSO's Standing Advisory Committee on Classification UC San Diego J. Coolman Personnel., 1986.; 891240 (Box 330, Folder 10)
- Nonprint Media Integration Assessment Survey. California State University, Chico., 1986.; 891239 (Box 330, Folder 11)
- Title VI updates for Wittenborg., 1986.; 891238 (Box 330, Folder 12)
- Size UC Libraries., 1977-1980.; 891237 (Box 330, Folder 13)
- Unified Annual Report., 1981/1982.; 891236 (Box 330, Folder 14)
- Association of Research Libraries statistics questionnaire., 1974-1983.; 891235 (Box 330, Folder 15-16)
- Size of the University of California Libraries [incomplete run]., 1947-1983.; 891234 (Box 330, Folder 17)
- Advertisements - positions., 1986-1987.; 891233 (Box 330, Folder 18-19)
- Popular American Music Archive., 1985-1986.; 891232 (Box 330, Folder 20)
- Law Library., 891231 (Box 330, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous budget and personnel., 1985-1987.; 891230 (Box 330, Folder 22)
- Unaffiliated libraries., 1986/1987.; 891229 (Box 330, Folder 23)
- Audit., 891228 (Box 330, Folder 24)
- Academic Affirmative Action., 1983-1985.; 891227 (Box 330, Folder 25)
- HEGIS (IPEDS) [Higher Education General Information Survey (Integrated Postsecondary Education Data System)]., 1988.; 891226 (Box 330, Folder 26)
- Chronological file for Rita Scherrei., 1983.; 891225 (Box 330, Folder 27)
- OCLC Invoices and Transfers of Expense., 1985-1986.; 891224 (Box 330, Folder 28)
- OCLC Invoice and Transfer of Expense., 1984-1985.; 891223 (Box 330, Folder 29)
- Network Operations Committee., 891222 (Box 331, Folder 1)
- Library Staff Association Executive Board minutes., 1972-1975.; 891221 (Box 331, Folder 2)
- Collection Development Committee., 891220 (Box 331, Folder 3)
- Library schedule of hours., 891219 (Box 331, Folder 4)
- Library Advisory Council., 1968-1971.; 891218 (Box 331, Folder 5-6)
- Staff Personnel Board newsletter., 891217 (Box 331, Folder 7)
- Staff Resource Committee roster, etc., 1968-1975.; 891216 (Box 331, Folder 8)
- Parking permits and information., 1974-1990.; 891215 (Box 331, Folder 9)
- University Open House [contains Library flyers]., 1956-1968.; 891214 (Box 331, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Library memos and correspondence., 1962-1968.; 891213 (Box 331, Folder 11)
- Health insurance and retirement brochures and memos., 1964-1990.; 891212 (Box 331, Folder 12)
- Financial system UCLA., 1981-1986.; 891211 (Box 331, Folder 13)
- Library memos., 1970-1971.; 891210 (Box 331, Folder 14)
- Administrative bulletins [campus]: accounting payroll, personnel., 1977-1991.; 891209 (Box 331, Folder 15)
- News & Views (newsletter of Labor Relations Division, Staff Personnel Department, UCLA)., 1977-1986.; 891208 (Box 331, Folder 16)
- UCLA Campus Supervisor's Update., 1987-1990.; 891207 (Box 331, Folder 17)
- UCLA Staff Assembly newsletter., 1987-1991.; 891206 (Box 331, Folder 18)
- Reference Desk and Catalog Information Service manuals., 197_-1986.; 891205 (Box 331, Folder 19)
- Data services - undergraduate students., 1976-1980.; 891204 (Box 331, Folder 20)
- Data services - UC coordinators., 1978-1982.; 891203 (Box 331, Folder 21)
- Computer searchers meetings, memos, etc., 1977-1981.; 891202 (Box 331, Folder 22)
- New York Times Information Bank., 1974-1976.; 891201 (Box 331, Folder 23)
- Database services - training and procedures., 1975-1992.; 891200 (Box 331, Folder 24)
- Database meetings and memos., 891199 (Box 331, Folder 25)
- Administrative memos - Chancellor's office., 1977-1991.; 891198 (Box 331, Folder 26)
- College space planning, 1991; 891172 (Box 332, Folder 1)
- Computer Reference Service Operations Group (CRSOG)., 891196 (Box 332, Folder 2)
- Data Services Advisory Committee, 1974-1975.; 891193 (Box 332, Folder 3)
- Data Services annual reports, etc., 1986-1991; 891195 (Box 332, Folder 4)
- Data Services - CLASS, COLRS, 1978-1980; 891164 (Box 332, Folder 5)
- Data Services Coordinators, 1977-1982; 891197 (Box 332, Folder 6)
- Ed/Psych (Education/Psychology Library), 1991-1992; 891173 (Box 332, Folder 7)
- Graduate subsidies for computer searches and brochures for Library services, 1978-1992; 891192 (Box 332, Folder 8)
- Library Master Plan process, 1986-1987.; 891177 (Box 332, Folder 9)
- MELVYL Instruction Committee (PAAC - Public Access Advisory Committee), 1986-1987; 891194 (Box 332, Folder 10)
- Northwest Campus Task Force report, 1991; 891183 (Box 332, Folder 11)
- Obsolete notes and information, 1966-1970; 891191 (Box 332, Folder 12)
- OCLC, 1991; 891181 (Box 332, Folder 13)
- OCLC First Search., 1991-1993.; 891179 (Box 332, Folder 14)
- Personnel Committee, 1968-1972; 891187 (Box 332, Folder 15-16)
- Powell Library building correspondence, 1985-1991; 891176 (Box 332, Folder 17)
- Powell Library pending, 1991; 891174 (Box 332, Folder 18)
- Powell loading dock, 1990-1991; 891171 (Box 332, Folder 19)
- Powell photocopier specifications, 1991; 891169 (Box 332, Folder 20)
- Public Access Advisory Committee (PAAC) Report, 1988-1992; 891186 (Box 332, Folder 21-23)
- Public Services Committee, 1968-1972; 891188 (Box 332, Folder 24)
- Research Library -furniture lists and miscellany for Unit 1(?), 1963-1964; 891190 (Box 332, Folder 25)
- Research Libraries Advisory Committee (RLAC) to OCLC Reciprocal Faculty Borrowing Program, 1989-1991; 891180 (Box 332, Folder 26)
- Rush Processing Committee charge and report, 1991; 891182 (Box 332, Folder 27)
- Schematic design and development (Powell), 1990-1991; 891165 (Box 332, Folder 28)
- Task Force Space, 1991; 891167 (Box 332, Folder 29)
- Technical Services Committee, 1968-1972; 891189 (Box 332, Folder 30)
- Telecommunications, 1990-1991; 891166 (Box 332, Folder 31)
- Towell shelving, 1990-1992; 891168 (Box 332, Folder 32)
- UCLA Library Space Plan, 1985; 891178 (Box 332, Folder 33)
- UC Library Systems Development Program, 3 volumes, 1971; 1316072 (Box 333, Folder 1-3)
- North Campus Library (University Research Library) Unit 2, 1968; 1316073; Includes Construction Documents and Addenda (Box 333, Folder 4-5)
- Catalog Department Meetings minutes, 1950-1962; 1316074 (Box 333, Folder 6)
- Rexroth Bibliography, 1967-1968; 1316075 (Box 333, Folder 7)
- Serials Processin Manual, 1970; 1316076 (Box 333, Folder 8)
- Management and Operations of the University of California. Vol. I The Library System of the University of California. Part II: Library Operations, 1972; 1316077 (Box 333, Folder 9)
- Powell Library Architectural Details Photographs, c. 1973; 1316078 (Box 333, Folder 10)
- Retirement Testimonial Samples, n.d.; 1316079 (Box 333, Folder 11)
- Management Review and Analysis Reports (MRAP), 1976; 1316080 (Box 333, Folder 13-14)
- Powell Library Building Floorplan, 1967; 1316082 (Box 333, Folder 18)
- Telephones, 1962; 1316083 (Box 333, Folder 19)
- Art Library, 1968; 1316084; Possible move of Theater Arts books to Art Library; Security (Box 333, Folder 20-21)
- UC Irvine Library Correspondence, 1966;1972; 1316085 (Box 333, Folder 22)
- Library Photographic Service, 1985; 1316086 (Box 333, Folder 23)
- STAT Computer Reference Services Statistical Program/UCLA Library, 1987; 1316087 (Box 333, Folder 24)
- Rita Scherrei Unit Head Memos, 1986;1987; 1316088; Questionnaires and Use of Faculty Center (Box 333, Folder 25)
- UCLA Map Library Monthly Statistics, 1962-1993; 1316089 (Box 333, Folder 26-32)
- UCLA Monthly Report of Holdings1987; 1991, 1316090 (Box 333, Folder 33-34)
- R. Barnai Correspondence, 1973; 1316091 (Box 333, Folder 35)
- Rename College Library as Undergraduate Library, 1963; 1316094 (Box 333, Folder 36)
- UCLA Campus Wide Database Computer Reference Services, 1991-1993; 1316095 (Box 333, Folder 37)
- No Box 334, 1316332
- Audio-Visual, 1968-1987; 1316335 (Box 335, Folder 1-2)
- Committee on Automation Human Factors Report, 1983; 1985; 1316339 (Box 335, Folder 3)
- Asian American Bibliographer, 1982-1986; 1316710; Includes annual reports for 1982/83, 1984/84 and 1985/86 (Box 335, Folder 4)
- University Library Audit Report 87-302501, 1987; 1316712 (Box 335, Folder 5)
- Auto-Graphics, 1986; 1316713 (Box 335, Folder 6)
- AVLINE, 1981; 1316714 (Box 335, Folder 7)
- African, 1987; 1316715 (Box 335, Folder 8)
- James Shinn and Frank Gille investigations and missing Belt Library books, 1980s; 1316719 (Box 335, Folder 9)
- BAMBAM Database, 1975-1984; 1316720 (Box 335, Folder 10)
- Banks Florilegium, 1980-1987; 1316722 (Box 335, Folder 11)
- Bibliographers and Bibliographic, 1978-1979; 1316724; Includes Committee on Products and Services, correspondence and responsibilities (Box 335, Folder 12-16)
- Henry J. Bruman Educational Foundation, 1974-1987; 1316726 (Box 335, Folder 17)
- Bindery Module and Costs, 1982-1988; 1316730 (Box 335, Folder 18-20)
- Biomedical Library, 1316731; Includes statistics (Box 335, Folder 21-23)
- Blackwell, 1987; 1316732 (Box 335, Folder 24)
- Blanket Plan, 1971-1985; 1316733 (Box 335, Folder 25)
- Book Budget, 1981-1987; 1316734 (Box 335, Folder 26)
- Borderline Project, 1982-1985; 1316736 (Box 335, Folder 27)
- Brazil, 1986-1987; 1316737 (Box 335, Folder 28)
- Brodart, 1985-1987; 1316738 (Box 335, Folder 29)
- BRS Information Technology, 1987; 1316739 (Box 335, Folder 30)
- Automation Development at UCLA, 1982-1985; 1316740 (Box 335, Folder 31)
- Campus Wide Database Computer Reference Services, 1991-1992; 1316741 (Box 335, Folder 32-33)
- Buying trips., 1963-1985.; 891162 (Box 336, Folder 1)
  Includes photos of Tsiang 1985 trip to China.
- Caldwell Collection., 1954-1977; 1981-1985.; 891161 (Box 336, Folder 2-3)
- California Spanish Language database., 891160 (Box 336, Folder 4)
- California State Polytechnic University, Pomona., 1985-1987.; 891159 (Box 336, Folder 5)
- California State University, Long Beach (CSULB)., 1987.; 891158 (Box 336, Folder 6)
- California State University, San Diego (CSUSD)., 891157 (Box 336, Folder 7)
- Campbell Book Contest., 1985-1987.; 891156; Karen Wittenborg file (Box 336, Folder 8)
- Card service., 891155 (Box 336, Folder 9)
- Carnegie-Mellon [computers]., 891154 (Box 336, Folder 10)
- Cataloguing, 1980-1984.; 891153; Includes AACRZ, Educational Program Ad Hoc Committee, and Supplement Project (CATSUP) OCLC Input. (Box 336, Folder 11-13)
- Chancellor's Communication Service (CCS), 1987; 1316795 (Box 336, Folder 14)
- CD-ROMs., 1987-1988.; 891149 (Box 336, Folder 15)
- Center for Afro-American Studies (CAAS)., 891148 (Box 336, Folder 16)
- Center for Applied Linguistics., 1987.; 891147 (Box 336, Folder 17)
- Center for Research Libraries., 1986-1987.; 891146 (Box 336, Folder 18-19)
- Chemical Abstracts Service., 1983-1984; 891145 (Box 336, Folder 20)
- Chemistry [Library]., 1986-1987.; 891144 (Box 336, Folder 21)
- Chicano Studies Center., 1981-1987; 891143 (Box 336, Folder 22)
- Clark Library., 1967-1987.; 891142 (Box 336, Folder 23)
- Circulation Department., 1982-1987.; 891141; Includes Advisory Committee (CAC) (Box 336, Folder 24-25)
- College Library., 1974-1987.; 891139 (Box 336, Folder 26)
- Collection Development, 1974-1987; 891138; Includes budget, problem areas, policy statements, correspondence, and Collection Development Committee, Council and Forum files. (Box 336, Folder 27-37)
- Columbia University Computer Systems, 1986; 1316828 (Box 337, Folder 1)
- Computers and Computer Planning, 1975-1986; 1316837; Includes Computer Plans and Committee, Committee on Resource Allocation and Service Requirements; Instructional Use (Box 337, Folder 2-7)
- CONOCO Report on German Literature and Geography, 1991; 1316838 (Box 337, Folder 8)
- CONSER, 1986-1987; 1316840; Includes Correspondence; Annual Report and Brochure; Membership; Planning Retreat; Committee correspondence: AI Advisory, Executive, and Policy; Task Force correspondence: Statistics, Vernacular, Micro and Macro Technology, Multiple Versions Database, Format Integration; (Box 337, Folder 9-28)
- Conversion Projects and Guidelines, 1979;1986; 1316841 (Box 337, Folder 29-30)
- Copyright, 1979-1982; 1316842; Includes Software copyright (Box 337, Folder 31-33)
- Library Catalog Cost Model Project., 891131; (ARL) (Box 338, Folder 1-2)
- Cost Recovery Group., 1983-1984.; 891129; Inter Library Loan costs (Box 338, Folder 3)
- Cummings Collection., 1081, 1985, 1993; 891128 (Box 338, Folder 4)
- Current Serials Title List (CSTL)., 1978-1980.; 891127 (Box 338, Folder 5)
- Databases and Database Access., 1985-1986.; 891126 (Box 338, Folder 6-7)
- Division of Library Automation (DLA), 1986-1987; 1316809; Includes California Academic Libraries List of Serials (CALLS) (Box 338, Folder 8-10)
- Deposit accounts., 1982-1983.; 891121 (Box 338, Folder 11)
- Special Collections. Annual report., 1987-1988.; 891120 (Box 338, Folder 12)
- Dissertations and theses., 1980; 891119; Memo concerning total number of dissertation and thesis copies to be deposited in University libraries (Box 338, Folder 13)
- University of California. Libraries. "A Plan for Development, 1978-1988.", 1977.; 891118 (Box 338, Folder 14)
- Oriental (East Asian) Library, 1975-1987; 891117 (Box 338, Folder 15-16)
- EDUCOM., 1987.; 891115 (Box 338, Folder 17)
- Education and Psychology Library., 1985-1987.; 891114 (Box 338, Folder 18)
- Emergencies., 1986; 891113 (Box 338, Folder 19)
- Engineering and Math Sciences (EMS)., 1985-1987.; 891112 (Box 338, Folder 20)
- English Reading Room., 1985-1988.; 891111 (Box 338, Folder 21)
- Ethnic Studies [Chicano Archival Program, proposal only]., 1981-1982.; 891110; Includes Chicano Archival program (proposal only) (Box 338, Folder 22-23)
- Exchanges and Exchange Program, 1981-1988.; 891108 (Box 338, Folder 24-25)
- Exhibits., 1985-1987.; 891106 (Box 338, Folder 26)
- UCLA/IBM Capacity and Resource Sharing Analysis., 1980; 891105 (Box 338, Folder 27-28)
- Faculty Book Chairs., 1972-1987.; 891104 (Box 338, Folder 29)
- Faxon Microcomputer, 1984-1987.; 891103 (Box 338, Folder 30-31)
- Fine Arts Libraries and Fine Arts Database, 1982; 1984-1987.; 891099 (Box 338, Folder 36-37)
- Finnish., 1973-1974.; 891097 (Box 338, Folder 38)
- Friends of the Library., 1985-1987.; 891096 (Box 338, Folder 39)
- Ethnomusicology Archive., 1083-1987; 891095 (Box 338, Folder 40)
- Computer Reference Services Statistical Program, 1989; 1316821 (Box 338, Folder 41)
- Public Services Committee (PSC) Meeting Minutes, 1988-1990; 1316822 (Box 338, Folder 42-44)
- Copyright, 1986-1988; 1316775 (Box 339, Folder 1)
- Educational Psychology Library Statistics, 1990-1991; 1316776 (Box 339, Folder 2)
- Fuji Project (optical digital technology), 1982-1983; 1316777 (Box 339, Folder 3)
- Gay and Lesbian Studies, 1979-1988; 1316778 (Box 339, Folder 4)
- Geology, 1980-1987; 1316779 (Box 330, Folder 5)
- Germanic collections, 1982-1987; 1316780; Includes Germanic bibliographer's annual reports 1984/85 and 1985/86 (Box 339, Folder 6)
- Getty Library, 1982-1988; 1316781; Includes Retrospective Conversion Project agreement and contract, Orion private database, grant program and library equipment (Box 339, Folder 7-14)
- Gloria Werner Memos, 1986-1988; 1316782; Includes letters (Box 339, Folder 15-18)
- Inter Library Loan (ILL), 1987-1991; 1316783 (Box 339, Folder 19)
- Melvyl, 1985-1993; 1316784 (Box 339, Folder 20)
- Metronet (MCLS), 1988-1992; 1316785; Includes surveys and grant applications (Box 339, Folder 21-23)
- Report of Library Holdings, 1990-1992; 1316786 (Box 339, Folder 24-25)
- Textbooks, 1316787 (Box 339, Folder 26)
- University Elementary School (UES), 1989-1990; 1316788 (Box 339, Folder 27)
- Undergraduate Library Service Task Force, 1977-1980; 1316789 (Box 339, Folder 28)
- Nicaraguan national bibliography., c. 1982-1987.; 891094 (Box 340, Folder 1)
- Nicaraguan national bibliography (includes correspondence)., c. 1982-1987.; 891093 (Box 340, Folder 2)
- Nijhoff., 1985.; 891092 (Box 340, Folder 3)
- Non-circulating reading center (NCRC) ad hoc Committee., 1985.; 891091 (Box 340, Folder 4)
- Non-circulating reading center NCRC., 1981-1985.; 891090 (Box 340, Folder 5)